ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- TWUA Committee Misc. 1970-1971 (Box 123, Folder 22)
- Sol Stetin Excerpts, ACTWU First Constitutional Convention, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 23)
- Hanes Project 1982 Plants (Box 123, Folder 24)
- Hanes Project 1982 Distribution (Box 123, Folder 25)
- Hanes Project 1982 Video (Box 123, Folder 26)
- Staff Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 123, Folder 27)
- Import Demonstration 1985 Legislation Textile and Apparel trade Enforcement Act (L. Smith) (Box 123, Folder 28)
- Income Tax Returns, The Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1928-1941 (Box 123, Folder 29)
- ACTWU Hanes Project #1, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 30)
- ACTWU Hanes Project #2, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Staff Coordinator Training Program, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 32)
- ACTWU Staff Coordinator Training Program #2, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 33)
- Conspiracy in Southern Textiles #1, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 34)
- Conspiracy in Southern Textiles #2, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 35)
- Conspiracy in Southern Textiles #3, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 36)
- TWUA Excerpts from Report to First Convention (1939) by TWOC and UTW (Box 124, Folder 1)
- TWUA Executive Minutes Council Minutes (current), 1976 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- Staff - Regional Assignments and Numerical Lists, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- Staff - Textile Division Local Union Affiliation (ACTWU), 1979-1986 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- Dues (Increases) 1975-1980 ACTWU Dues Comm "papers" & Fact Sheet (Box 124, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Convention 1984 #1 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Convention 1984 #2 (Box 124, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Convention 1984 #3 (Box 124, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated TWUA Correspondence Preceding Merger Convention January-June 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 124, Folder 9)
- ACWA - Constitution and By-Laws (Before Merger), 1974 (Box 124, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Constitution- Interpretations 1977-, 1982-1984 (Box 124, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Constitutional Amendments Referendum Election 1983 (Box 124, Folder 12)
- Administratorship - Catawba Valley Joint Board 4/10/87 Administrator: Nick Builder, 1987-1988 (Box 124, Folder 13)
- Southern Catawba Valley Joint Board (General File)1984-, 1984-1987 (Box 124, Folder 14)
- Catawba Valley Joint Board Edward Nichols 1986-, 1986-1987 (Box 124, Folder 15)
- Catawba Valley Joint Board Meeting. Friday, Nov. 7th, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 16)
- Southern Catawba Valley Joint Board Charter & Organization of Joint Board. 7-22-83, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 17)
- Managerial Rebate Increases to Joint Board Managers. 10/88, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 18)
- Managerial Rebates 1988, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 19)
- Managerial Rebates 1987 (Box 124, Folder 20)
- Managerial Rebates 1986 (Box 124, Folder 21)
- Managerial Rebates 1985 (Box 124, Folder 22)
- Managerial Rebates 1984 (Box 124, Folder 23)
- Managerial Rebate Letters 4/83 New Rebates Effective 4/1/83, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 24)
- Managerial Rebates Record of Joint Board Monthly Rebates (from year to year), 1981-1982 (Box 124, Folder 25)
- Managerial Rebates Miscellaneous 1982 (Box 124, Folder 26)
- Managerial Rebates 1981 (Box 124, Folder 27)
- Joint Board Managers On International Payroll(F.O.U.R. & Non-F.O.U.R), 1977-1981 (Box 124, Folder 28)
- Real Estate: Memo to M. Bourne May 16, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 29)
- Textile Divison Reports Real Estate 1982 (Box 124, Folder 30)
- Real Estate - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978-1987 (Box 124, Folder 31)
- New Orleans Real Estate, 1978-1982 (Box 124, Folder 32)
- Real Estate - Local 253 West Columbia, SC, 1980-1981 (Box 124, Folder 33)
- TWUA Holding Company Property Rocky Mount, NC (Local 1728) (Phillips Fibers, Inc.), 1981-1983 (Box 124, Folder 34)
- Real Estate - Property of TWUA Locals and Joint Boards (1977-78), 1977-1978 (Box 124, Folder 35)
- Canadian Locals & joint boards All Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- Mr. John Alleruzzo, Canadian director ACTWU, AFL-CIO, CLC 15 Gervais Drive, Suite 700 Don Mills, Ontario Canada M3C 1Y8, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- Noel Beasley, Vice President ACTWU Midwest Regional Joint Board 333 South Ashland Blvd, Suite 205 Chicago, IL 60607-2773, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- Mr. Edward Clark, Jr., Vice President ACTWU N.E. Regional Joint Board 867 State Road North Dartmouth, MA 02747-1892, 1988-1991 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- Ms. Clayola Brown, Vice President ACTWU, Amalgamated Service. & Allied Industries Joint Board 99 University Place -- 8th Fl. New York, NY 10003-4561, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 5)
- Mr. Anthony Costanza, Vice President ACTWU, Rochester Joint Board 750 East Avenue Rochester, NY 14607-2188, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 6)
- Ms. Olga Diaz, Vice President ACTWU, Shirt & Leisurewear Division New York Joint Board 31 West 15th Street - 6th Fl. New York, NY10011, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- Mr. Bruce Dunton, vice President ACTWU Mid-Atlantic Region Joint Board 903 Russell Avenue Gaithersburg, Md 20879, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 8)
- Pennsylvania Merger, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 9)
- Bruce Dunton's Building, 1989-1991 (Box 125, Folder 10)
- Mr. John Fox, Vice President ACTWU Philadelphia Joint Board 22 South 22nd Street Philadelphia, A 19103-3301, 1989-1993 (Box 125, Folder 11)
- Mr. Nicholas Hambas, Vice President ACTWU New York joint Board 31 west 15th Street New York, NY 10011-6880, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 12)
- Mr. John Hudson, Vice President ACTWU New York-New Jersey Joint Board 99 University Place, 3rd Floor New York, NY 10003-4580, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 13)
- Mr. Arthur Hoover, Vice President ACTWU Chicago & Central States 333 South Ashland Boulevard Chicago, IL 60607-2773, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 14)
- Mr. James Johnson, Vice President ACTWU South Carolina Coastal District P.O. Box 157 Andrews, SC 29510, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 15)
- Mr. Richard McFayden, Vice President ACTWU Greater Northeastern Joint Board. P.O. Box 448 Williamantic, CT 06226-0448, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 16)
- Mr. Andrew Mattey, Vice President ACTWU Pennsylvania Joint Board 1720 W. Market Street Pottsville, PA 17901, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 17)
- Ted Gatto Scranton-Wilkes Barre JB ACTWU Line St & O'Neill Hwy Dunmore PA 18512-1492, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 18)
- Barbara Mejia California Joint Board ACTWU 2501 South Hill St Los Angles CA 90007-2782, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 19)
- Mr. Carmen Papale, Vice President ACTWU Baltimore Regional Joint Board. 1505 Eutaw Place Baltimore, MD 21217-3698, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 20)
- So. Jersey joint Board Administratorship; Terminated 10/19/88 (Box 125, Folder 21)
- Bruce Raynor Southern Tex Reg J B ACTWU 510 Plaza Dr-Rm 1520 College Park GA 30349, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 22)
- Southern Merger, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 23)
- Carleton Rakes + Sidney Young Bi County & North Carolina Joint Board ACTWU P O Box 368 Eden NC 27288-0368, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 24)
- Ms. Joan Suarez, Vice President ACTWU Southwest Region Joint Board., 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 25)
- San Antonio District, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 26)
- Anthony Micelli Central & South Jersey Joint Board, 1987-1988 (Box 125, Folder 27)
- Robert L Redlo Hudson Valley Joint Board ACTWU 512 Warren St Hudson NY 12534-2802, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 28)
- Joseph Gallagher Greater Northern Joint Board ACTWU 219 West First St Oswego NY 13126-2590, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 29)
- R L Roper Western Carolinas Joint Board ACTWU P O Box 705 Mountain Home NC 28758, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 30)
- Nick Builder Catawba Valley Joint Board ACTWU Drawer 2834-CRS Rock Hill SC 29730, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 31)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 32)
- Wilfredo Medina Puerto Rico Joint Board ACTWU PO Box 9053 Santurce PR 00908, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 33)
- New York Retail, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 34)
- Local 340A, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 35)
- Western New York Joint Board. Doris Heath, Manager, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 36)
- New York Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board October, 1993 Washington DC (Box 126, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Resolutions, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 3)
- GEB Meeting May 17-20, 1993 A. Leovy (Box 126, Folder 4)
- GEB - Jan 1993 Financial + Administration, 1991-1993 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Meeting -- Las Vegas January 11-15, 1993, 1991-1993 (Box 126, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board Mtg November 18-20, 1992 New York, NY (Box 126, Folder 7)
- GEB Meeting New York, NY September 14-16, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board November 14-16, 1991 Detroit (Box 126, Folder 9)
- Secretary-Treasurers Report GEB Meeting, May 11-15, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 10)
- GEB Meeting, NYC May 11-15, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 11)
- GEB San Antonio February 1992 (Box 126, Folder 12)
- GEB 9/23, 9/26, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 13)
- Secretary Treasurer's Report Back-up Documents Sept 1991 (Box 126, Folder 14)
- Secretary Treasurers Report, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 15)
- Textiles and Apparel in NAFTA #1, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 16)
- Textiles and Apparel in NAFTA #2, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board May, 1991, New York, NY (Box 126, Folder 18)
- 1987 National Clo. Contract (Box 126, Folder 19)
- Clothing Negotiations 1987 (Box 126, Folder 20)
- Clothing Negotiations 1987 #2 (Box 126, Folder 21)
- Clothing Negotiations 1988 (Box 126, Folder 22)
- Post Survey Excerpts on 2nd Quarter Dept. Store Clothing Sales, 1989 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- National Clothing Industry Labor Management Committee, Inc., 1989 (Box 127, Folder 2)
- Labor-Management Committee (LMC), 1989 (Box 127, Folder 3)
- Labor-Management Committee #2, 1989 (Box 127, Folder 4)
- 1990 National Clothing Agreement (Box 127, Folder 5)
- 1990 Clothing Negotiations - Proposals (Box 127, Folder 6)
- 1990 Clothing Negotiations - Insurance (Box 127, Folder 7)
- 1990 Clothing Negotiations - General (Box 127, Folder 8)
- National Clothing LMC Committee, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 9)
- Memorandum (Clothing Fund Executive Committee), 1991 (Box 127, Folder 10)
- Background Data, 1989-1990 (Box 127, Folder 11)
- Clothing Unions 1990-1991 #1 (Box 127, Folder 12)
- Clothing Unions 1990-1991 #2 (Box 127, Folder 13)
- Clothing Unions 1990-1991 #3 (Box 127, Folder 14)
- Levi's Works Council Con. Brussels June 16-18, 1993 (Box 127, Folder 15)
- Minutes - Sourcing Committee Meeting, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 16)
- Levi Strauss 1993 and 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 127, Folder 17)
- Levi's /ACTWU Steering Committee, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 18)
- ACTWU/Levi Conference February 4-5, 1993 Baltimore Md (Box 128, Folder 1)
- Levi Strauss 1992 (Box 128, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment 1988 Negotiations (Box 128, Folder 3)
- Cotton Garment Inc., 1988 (Box 128, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment Insurance Negotiating Fund, 1989-1990 (Box 128, Folder 5)
- Arkansas District Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 6)
- 1991 Cotton Garment Insurance Supplement - "Extra" (Box 128, Folder 7)
- Cotton Garment Agreements (Enro Shirt co.), 1991-1992 (Box 128, Folder 8)
- Cotfund Insurance, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 9)
- Cotfund Insurance #2, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 10)
- 1990 Cotton Garment Settlement, 1990-1991 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- Cotfund Agreement & Declaration of Trust, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 12)
- Cotfund - Investment Committee, 1993 (Box 128, Folder 13)
- "Cot" Fund - Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 128, Folder 14)
- "Cot-fund" 1992+1993, 1991-1993 (Box 128, Folder 15)
- Cotton Garment Agreements, 1988-1992 (Box 128, Folder 16)
- Cotton Garment Agreements #2, 1990 (Box 128, Folder 17)
- 1994 Cotton Garment Negotiations (Box 128, Folder 18)
- Cotfund Insurance Supplements, 1990-1991 (Box 128, Folder 19)
- Cotfund Supplemental and Extension Agreement, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 20)
- Cotton Garment & Allied Industries Fund, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 21)
- Facts for Bargaining: Cotton Garment July 1994 (Box 128, Folder 22)
- Alternate Sourcing; Clothing, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- Complaints 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Constitutional Amendments, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Convention Greetings, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 4)
- Convention Greetings to Other Unions, 1990-1991 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Pending Resolutions File, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 6)
- 1993 Convention Guest Letters Pd (Box 129, Folder 7)
- 1993 Convention, 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- Constitutional Amendments, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 9)
- Guest Speakers - 1993 Convention. (Box 129, Folder 10)
- 1993 Convention. Guest Speakers "Acceptances" (Box 129, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, Feb. 1989 (Box 129, Folder 12)
- Correspondence. March, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 13)
- Correspondence. April, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 14)
- Correspondence. May, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 15)
- Correspondence. June, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 16)
- Correspondence. Juli, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 17)
- Correspondence. August, 1989, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 18)
- Correspondence. September, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 19)
- Correspondence. October, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 20)
- Correspondence. November 1989 (Box 129, Folder 21)
- Correspondence. December, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 22)
- 1992+1993 Complaints (Box 129, Folder 23)
- Complaint File - 1991 (Box 129, Folder 24)
- Complaints - 1990 (Box 129, Folder 25)
- 1990 Correspondence File (Box 129, Folder 26)
- Correspondence Chronologic file 1991 (Box 129, Folder 27)
- Damon creations Inc., 1990-1991 (Box 129, Folder 28)
- 1992 Correspondence "Chronologic File" (Box 129, Folder 29)
- 1989 Dues Increase (Box 129, Folder 30)
- Dues Increases & Charters May, 1988 GEB Meeting (Box 129, Folder 31)
- 1988 Dues Increases Memo (Box 129, Folder 32)
- Sec'y-Treasurer's report for GEB February 22, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 33)
- Requests for New Charters & Requests for Revocation of Existing Charter - Finance, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 34)
- Requests for New Charters & Revocation for Existing Charters - 1988 (Box 129, Folder 35)
- Dues Increase - 1987 (Box 129, Folder 36)
- Requests for Dues Increases 1988 Feb. GEB (Box 129, Folder 37)
- ACTWU Membership Dues 1986 (Box 129, Folder 38)
- ACTWU Finance department 1984 (Box 129, Folder 39)
- ACTWU Dues Increases 1976 Locals& Joint Boards., 1985-1986 (Box 129, Folder 40)
- Eagle/Gant, 1989-1991 (Box 129, Folder 41)
- Eagle/Gant Duplicate Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 129, Folder 42)
- LMC - 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Four, 1990-1994 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- F.O.U.R Agreements, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 3)
- Contract 1987 (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Gitman Brothers, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 5)
- Greif Negotiations #1, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Greif Negotiations #2, 1991-1993 (Box 130, Folder 7)
- Greif Negotiations #3, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 8)
- Greif Negotiations #4, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 9)
- Greif Company, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 10)
- Hart, Schaffner & Marx 1992 (Box 130, Folder 11)
- Hearing Officer Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 130, Folder 12)
- Hearing Officer Reports #2, 1990 (Box 130, Folder 13)
- Histadrut Dinner in Honor of Arthur Loevy, May 6, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 14)
- Histadrut, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Finances, 1987-1988 (Box 130, Folder 16)
- International Union of Allied Novelty and Production Workers, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 17)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting October 27-29, 1991 Prague (Box 130, Folder 18)
- Juvenile Shoe Corp. #1, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 19)
- Juvenile Shoe Corp. #2, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 20)
- Legal Department, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Legal Department #2, 1989-1991 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Legal Dept. Benton Bell, 1989-1990 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Legal Dept. Memos - 1989 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Local 2h Legal Expense, 1988-1989 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Louisville Manufacturing, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Merrill Lynch, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 7)
- Montreal Law Suit, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 8)
- N.Y.S Council of Senior Citizens, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 9)
- Non-union Shirt & Nightwear Workers, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 10)
- O.S.H.A., 1989-1991 (Box 131, Folder 11)
- Per Capita, 1988-1990 (Box 131, Folder 12)
- Per Capita comparisons 1988 (Box 131, Folder 13)
- Ron Rosenburg, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 14)
- Rudd Manufacturing Co, Incorporated, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 15)
- Reallocation of Resources C. Sallee Memos to Joint Boards., 1987-1989 (Box 131, Folder 16)
- Organizing Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 131, Folder 17)
- Re-Allocation of Resources Responses from Joint Boards, 1987-1988 (Box 131, Folder 18)
- Spencer Hays, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Shirt & Leisurewear Health & Welfare Fund Merger, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 20)
- Arthur Loevy; SUB, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 21)
- Textile & Home Products, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 22)
- Transfer Cards, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 23)
- Textile Workers Health Plan, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 24)
- ACTWU Textile Staff Retirement Plan, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 25)
- Amalgamated Bank Meeting with Arthur Loevy, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 26)
- Annual return-Textile Staff Retirement Plan, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 27)
- ACTWU, Workers Pension and Health Fund, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Health Plan Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 132, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers Health Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers Pension Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 4)
- Frank A. Lucas Sr., 1989 (Box 132, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, 1990 (Box 132, Folder 6)
- TWPF - Minutes 1987 (Box 132, Folder 7)
- Trip to soviet Union July, 1990 (Box 132, Folder 8)
- Work in America Institute, Inc., 1988 (Box 132, Folder 9)
- Washable Fund, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 10)
- Westmill Clothes, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 11)
- Window Program, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 12)
- DSA Dinner for J. Sheinkman, 1992 (Box 132, Folder 13)
- Zensen Meeting, 1994 (Box 132, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Eastern Strike Fund, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Clinton Swan Company, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Convention October, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1991 Detroit, Mi. Delegates List (Box 133, Folder 4)
- 1989 AFL-CIO Convention. (Box 133, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Convention, Florida Begins October 26, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Updated Surveys, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 7)
- Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 8)
- Bushelman - 1993 (Box 133, Folder 9)
- Bushelman - 1991 (Box 133, Folder 10)
- Bond Clothing, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 11)
- Canada, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 12)
- City of Hope Dinner, Skenton Centre - NY Oct 19, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 13)
- Clothing Manufacturers Assoc., 1989-1991 (Box 133, Folder 14)
- Ron Rosenburg, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 15)
- Beck File, 1991-1993 (Box 133, Folder 16)
- To; Arthur Loevy #1, 1988-1989 (Box 133, Folder 17)
- To; Arthur Loevy #2, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 18)
- "After Six", 1992-1994 (Box 133, Folder 19)
- Associate Member Organization "AMO", 1991 (Box 133, Folder 20)
- Arthur Loevy, Financial Statements, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Bank, 1987-1989 (Box 133, Folder 22)
- Central Executive Board Feb. 28- March 2, 1994 New York City (Box 134, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Meeting, May 17-19, 1994 New York City (Box 134, Folder 2)
- GEB July 26, 1994 NYC (Box 134, Folder 3)
- September 1994 GEB Montreal, Canada (Box 134, Folder 4)
- Collection Control Department, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 5)
- July 1995 Collection Control Dept. (Box 134, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 7)
- New Jersey region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 8)
- New England Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 9)
- Northeast Dept., 1995 (Box 134, Folder 10)
- Ohio, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 11)
- Eastern Penna. Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 12)
- South Jersey, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 13)
- Upper South, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 14)
- Southeast, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 15)
- Midwest Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 16)
- Western States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 17)
- Bay Area, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 18)
- Master Agreement, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 19)
- Local 23-25, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 20)
- Local 91-105, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 21)
- Central States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 22)
- Local 62-32, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 23)
- Local 66-40, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 24)
- Local 132-98, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 25)
- Local 102, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 26)
- Local 155, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 27)
- Local 99, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 28)
- New York State, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 29)
- Collections Control, 1996-1995 (Box 134, Folder 30)
- Collection Control, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 31)
- August 1995 Collection Control, 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 32)
- Local 89-22-1, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 33)
- New Jersey Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 34)
- New England Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 35)
- Northeast Dept., 1995 (Box 134, Folder 36)
- Ohio, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 37)
- Eastern Penna. Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 38)
- South Jersey, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 39)
- Upper South, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 40)
- Southeast, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 41)
- Midwest Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 42)
- Western States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 43)
- Bay Area, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 44)
- Master Agreement, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 45)
- Local 23-25, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 46)
- Local 91-105, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 47)
- Central States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 48)
- Local 62-32, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 49)
- Local 66-40, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 50)
- Local 132-98, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 51)
- Local 102, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 52)
- Local 155, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 53)
- Local 99, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 54)
- New York State, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 55)
- October 1995 Collection Control Dept. (Box 134, Folder 56)
- Local 89-22-1, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 57)
- New Jersey, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 58)
- New England Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 59)
- Northeast Dept., 1995 (Box 134, Folder 60)
- Ohio, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 61)
- South Jersey, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 62)
- Upper South, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 63)
- Southeast, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 64)
- Midwest Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 65)
- Western States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 66)
- Bay Area, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 67)
- Master Agreement, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 68)
- Local 23-25, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 69)
- Local 91-105, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 70)
- Central States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 71)
- Local 62-32, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 72)
- Local 66-40, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 73)
- Local 132-98, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 74)
- Local 102, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 75)
- local 155, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 76)
- Local 99, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 77)
- New York State, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 78)
- September 1995 Collection Control Dept. (Box 134, Folder 79)
- Local 89-22-1, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 80)
- New Jersey region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 81)
- New England Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 82)
- Northeast Dept., 1995 (Box 134, Folder 83)
- Ohio, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 84)
- Eastern Penna. Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 85)
- South Jersey, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 86)
- Upper South, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 87)
- Southeast, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 88)
- Midwest Region, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 89)
- Western States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 90)
- Bay Area, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 91)
- Master Agreement, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 92)
- Local 23-25, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 93)
- Local 91-105, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 94)
- Central States, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 95)
- Local 62-32, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 96)
- Local 66-40, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 97)
- Local 132-98, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 98)
- Local 102, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 99)
- Local 155, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 100)
- Local 99, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 101)
- New York State, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 102)
- UNITE General Office Administrative Department, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 103)
- Former ACTWU Organizational Region & Departments, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 104)
- UNITE Organization Regions & Departments, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 105)
- S.A.F.E, 1993 (Box 134, Folder 106)
- AMS Evaluations, 1991-1994 (Box 134, Folder 107)
- Levi's /ACTWU Steering Committee, Misc., 1991-1995 (Box 134, Folder 108)
- Hourly Rewards, 1993-1994 (Box 134, Folder 109)
- ACTWU/Levi Partnership Meetings, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 1)
- Irwin Soloman, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 2)
- UNITE General Fund and ILGWU Funds, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 3)
- Ted Gatto, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 4)